collegedata.com 2018-04-01

# CollegeData - Privacy Policy

CollegeData Privacy Policy

What is the purpose of this Privacy Policy?

At CollegeData, a service provided by 1st Financial Bank USA, your privacy is important to us. We have established standards that govern our collection, use, retention, and protection of information about you in connection with your use of this Site.

What information do we collect from users and how is it used?

1st Financial Bank USA is the sole owner of the information collected on this Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others or use it in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy.

1st Financial Bank USA collects information from our users at several different points on our Site.

Sign Up  
When you sign up for CollegeData, we ask that you provide to us certain personally identifiable information. We request this information in order to verify compliance with the CollegeData Site User Agreement and applicable federal, state and local law and for identification and security purposes. We may also ask that you provide to us certain other information, such as how you heard about CollegeData and what college planning resources you are using or have used.

Data Locker  
When you use certain tools on this Site and when you save items to your Data Locker, such information will be retained in a file specific to you.

Collection of Personal Information from Children Under Thirteen  
1st Financial Bank USA does not knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to sign up for our services.

Do-Not-Track Signals from Users' Browsers  
We do not use technology that responds to Do-Not-Track signals from your web browser.

Collection and Use of Information  
We collect information on this Site that you provide to us. We also use "cookies" to collect aggregate information about Site usage and our users' browsing activities, which information is not user specific. A "cookie" is a small text file that a Web site may provide to your browser when you visit the site. We use cookies on the Site which enable third parties to provide us with better insights into the use of the Site or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. The Site may also link to third parties' sites, which parties may collect information about a consumer's online activities over time and across different websites. We do not use "cookies" to collect or store personally identifiable information, provided that we use a "cookie" to store a unique identification number assigned to you that may be used to customize Site content and services for individual users. While you may modify the settings of your browser to prevent acceptance of "cookies," you must enable "cookies" to access areas of the Site that require log in. The information we collect on this Site may be used to market our financial products and services to you and also allows us to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze Site usage, and to improve and customize our content, product offerings, and services.

Can users access their information to correct or update it?

Users who have signed up for CollegeData can access the information they have previously entered to correct or update it by logging into the Site and going to their Data Locker or other feature in which they initially entered the information. 

Information that is captured automatically by our site (such as visit date and time, IP address, device type, and pages visited) is not information that the user enters directly, and they cannot access or change it.

Whom does 1st Financial Bank USA disclose personal information to?

With unaffiliated third parties. We may reveal information about you to third parties not affiliated with 1st Financial Bank: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the information is provided to applicable rating agencies of the financial institution, persons assessing the institution's compliance with industry standards, and the institution's attorneys, accountants, and auditors; (5) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (6) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.), or in connection with a proposed or actual securitization, secondary market sale (including sales of servicing rights), or similar transaction related to a transaction of the consumer; or (7) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

With affiliated third parties. We may reveal information about you to third parties affiliated with 1st Financial Bank USA to assist us with important risk management, legal, Internet, securitization, account-acquisition and marketing services.

What are the policies of 1st Financial Bank USA regarding promotional emails it may send?

A user has the right to opt out of promotional e-mails sent by us or one of our agents by clicking the unsubscribe link included in the e-mail to indicate that the user wants to opt out of receiving future promotional e-mails. We may send you e-mails about transactions with us or about your account even though you may have opted out of receiving promotional e-mails.

What are the policies of linked sites and other third parties?

This Privacy Policy only addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from you. You should be aware that when you are on the Site, you can be directed to other Web sites that are beyond our control, and 1st Financial Bank USA is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or the content of those linked Web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy whenever interacting with any Web site.

What security measures does the Site employ?

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard your personally identifiable information, including the information we collect on this Site. Our security procedures are aimed at preventing unauthorized access to such information and are reviewed and audited periodically for compliance with federal standards. To help protect the privacy of data you transmit through use of this Site, all communication of personally identifiable information is transmitted over HTTPS using Transport Layer Security (TLS). Your registration and log in information are always transmitted using TLS, as is information submitted on an Admissions Profile or when using the EFC Calculator. We also recommend users access the Site with a browser that supports 128-bit encryption.

We require registering users to select a password to protect access to their information. Please do not share this information with others; any interaction with the Site using your e-mail address and password will be considered authorized by you.

How will I know about changes in the Privacy Policy?

1st Financial Bank USA reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes.

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this Site, you may request more information by writing to us at:

Privacy  
1st Financial Bank USA  
P.O. 7300  
North Sioux City, SD 57049
